class Journalism {
  static const List<Map<String, dynamic>> thirdMonthly = <Map<String, dynamic>>[
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'lead',
      'question': 'is the most important part of a news story.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'lead',
      'question':
          'it gives readers the most important information in a clear, concise, and interesting manner.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'the five w’s and h',
      'question': 'decide which aspect of the story.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'conflict',
      'question': 'good stories have this.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'specificity',
      'question':
          'though you are essentially summarizing information in most leads, try to be as specific as possible.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'brevity',
      'question':
          'readers want to know why the story matters to them and they won’t wait long for the answer.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'active sentences',
      'question': 'strong verbs will make your lead lively and interesting.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'passive leads',
      'question': 'incomplete reporting is often a source of these.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'audience and context',
      'question': 'take into account what your reader already knows.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'honesty',
      'question': 'a lead is an implicit promise to your readers.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'flowery language',
      'question':
          'many beginning writers make the mistake of overusing adverbs and adjectives in their leads.',
    },
    <String, String>{
      'answer': 'unnecessary words or phrases',
      'question': 'watch out for unintentional redundancy.',
    }
  ];
}
